rove.com 2019-12-07

# Privacy Policy | Karl Rove

At Karl Rove & Company we are committed to protecting your privacy online. While using our website, you do not have to identify yourself or divulge personal information. If you should choose to give us your personal information, you decide the amount of information you wish to provide.

Karl Rove & Company will occasionally update this privacy policy as changes to the site necessitate it. We encourage you to periodically review this policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information.  Our site links to a limited number of other websites.  Karl Rove & Company is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of these websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements for each website you visit.

On our sign-up forms on rove.com we may ask for your name, address, telephone number,  email address.  If you should choose to give us your personal information, you decide the amount of information you wish to provide. We will only use your information to provide you information about us or news related to other George W. Bush administration officials. We may also use your zip code and state to send you email messages about upcoming events or activities in your area.

Cookies:

A cookie is a very small text file that is placed on your hard drive. Cookies do not contain any personal information about you. You can opt-out of our use of cookies by disabling cookies on your browser.  We use cookies to tailor your experience on our site according to the preferences you have specified. When you visit the Karl Rove & Company website we only access the cookie file that we have stored on your computer. We cannot and do not access any information stored in a cookie by other websites. 

IP Addresses and Log File Data.

We log the IP address, which is the location of your computer or network on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We also use page hits in the collective to track the popularity of pages that people visit in order to improve the visitor experience. 

Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998:

We comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying FTC regulations establish United States federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet. We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. Our site is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 13.

How can you contact us?

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, the information we have collected from you online, the practices of this site or your interaction with this website, send email to us here. [ privacy@rove.com](mailto:privacy@rove.com)
